Fred Starner Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Miscellany, 1966 - 1985; 6; Box: 3
  - Fundraising letter with Toshi and Peter Seeger's return address, circa 1975; 34 (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - Board Meetings, 18 January 1976- 5 December 1976; 35 (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - Clearwater Maintenance [includes letter from Pete Seeger referenced in board minutes from 7 March 1976], 3 January 1976- 19 April 1976; 36 (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - Correspondence from [Director] Walter P. Bowers, II to Angela McGill [sic] [President], 16 January 1976; 37 (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - PCB Controversy New York Times articles- "2 State Officials Split in Controversy Over Discharge of PCB's Into Hudson" and "What Price Jobs?", 16 January 1976, 26 January 1976; 38 (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - Statement of Introduction to Hudson River Sloop Restoration's Programs, 1 March 1976; 1 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Minutes of the Environmental Action Committee, 26 April 1976; 2 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - "The Talk of the Town" in The New Yorker, circa summer 1976; 3 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Dave Seymour's Hike for the Hudson River, August 1976; 4 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - "Clearwater Calls on EPA to Rais PCB Money to $10 M[illion]" and Correspondence from Angela Magill [President] to Russel Train {Environmental Protection Agency], 10 September 1976; 5 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Report of the [By-Laws Review] Committee to the Board of Directors of the Hudson River Sloop Restoration, Inc., circa 4 November 1976; 6 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Correspondence from [Board Member] Walt to Angela Magill [President], 11 December 1976; 7 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - 1976 Annual Hudson River Sloop Restoration, Inc. Meeting, circa December 1976; 8 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Membership and Endowment Fund Proposals, 1976; 9 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Weekly Highlights, 1976; 10 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Board Meeting Materials- Minutes, Memo from President Angela Magill, Financial Report, 9 January 1977- 20 November 1977; 11 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Clearwater Financial Program, 15 March 1977; 12 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Monthly Membership Reports and Weekly Highlights, March 1977- April 1977; 13 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Lobbying and Maintenance of Tax Exempt Status, 1 April 1977; 14 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Clearwater Fall Seminar [including committee outlines], circa 1 October 1977- 2 October 1977; 15 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Memo to the Board of Directors from Angela Magill- fundraising appeal, 23 November 1977; 16 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Annual Meeting of the Clearwater, 4 December 1977; 17 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - 1977 Clearwater Treasurer's Report, December 1977; 18 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - List of Board of Directors Members, 1977; 19 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Board Meeting Materials- Minutes and Treasurer's Reports, 22 January 1978- 17 December 1978; 20 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Anti-Nuclear Power Policy, circa 24 June 1978- 25 June 1978; 21 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Fundraising Plan- Memo, Mailings, and Corporation List, circa 11 August 1978- December 1978; 22 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - 1978 Clearwater Treasurer's Report- For Nine Months Ending, 31 August 1978; 23 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - 1978 Clearwater Annual Meeting, 24 September 1978; 24 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Executive Director's Report, 15 October 1978; 25 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 25 February 1979- 18 August 1979; 26 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 22 September 1984- 18 November 1984; 27 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Sloop Club Charter Guidelines, circa 1984-1985; 28 (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - Board Meeting Materials- Minutes, Agenda, resolution honoring Sarah L. Johnston, 11 January 1985- 25 August 1985; 29 (Folder 39, Box 3)